Name: Sabit Alizade

Contact Information:

- Email: <u>sabit@engineer.com</u>
- Phone: +994706717474
- Github: <u>https://github.com/sabitalizade</u>
- Linkedin: https://linkedin.com/in/sabitalizade

- Address: Baku, Azerbaijan - Website: https://sabitalizade.com

Summary:

Experienced software developer with 2 years of experience in full-stack web development using JavaScript, Node js, React, Docker, Git, Mongodb and SQL. Strong background in developing, testing, and deploying software solutions. Proven ability to adapt to new technologies and work in a team environment.

Education:

- Master of Regulation of Economy, Baku State University, Baku, Azerbaijan (2017-2019)
- Bachelor of Economy, Nakhchivan State University, Nakhchivan, Azerbaijan (2013-2017)

Experience:

Software Developer, EiLink R&D (2022-Present)

- Worked as a frontend developer and then as a full-stack developer on a supply chain management product.
- Developed and maintained software applications using JavaScript, Node.js, React, and SQL.
- Implemented Microservice architecture, and developed a notification socket service using Node.js and MongoDB.
- Worked in an Agile development environment and collaborated with other developers and stakeholders to understand requirements and design software solutions.

JavaScript Developer, AT-Geotech (2021-2022)

- Developed an ERP system using jQuery, React, and SQL.
- Worked with a team to understand the requirements and design software solutions.
- Participated in code reviews to ensure high-quality codebase.

Frontend Developer, Meal Ordering Startup (2021-Present)

- Developed 90% of a merchant app for a meal ordering startup similar to Uber Eats using React, Redux, and Ant Design.
- Continuously support and maintain the app, fixing bugs and adding new features.
- Worked with a team to understand the requirements and design software solutions.
- Participated in code reviews to ensure high-quality codebase.

Skills:

- Proficient in JavaScript, Node.js, React, Redux, SQL, MongoDB, Docker, Git, Knex.js, and Express.js.
- Experience with Microservice architecture and Go Lang.
- Strong understanding of web development principles and best practices.
- Experience with Agile development methodologies.
- Strong problem-solving and analytical skills.